Music Plays I look up
to the stars and reach
for the sky I believe
in tomorrow if we try!
Hey!
Come on, let's go, everybody!
Oh, we share the music!
We share the music!
Come on, let's go, baby, baby!
Oh, we share the one dream!
Come on, let's go, everybody!
Oh, we share the good times!
We share the good times!
Let's go, baby, baby,
always share the one world.
It's hard to see for you and me.
Through the darkness
that is in this world.
So hard to see, but to believe
In where we need to go.
Yes, you and me, it's true that we
Feel the rush brought on by this world.
Through head to feet, I feel the
beat Getting me to walk on, oh yeah.
Share the music, no matter what.
Share the one dream, believe in yourself.
Share the good times, take my hand now.
Share the one world now.
I look up to the stars.
And reach for the sky.
No matter what.
I'll try no matter how high.
So let us go.
Beyond, far and wide.
I believe in tomorrow.
If we try high.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Come on, let's go everybody.
Oh, we share the music.
Come on, let's go baby, baby.
Oh, we share the one world.
Oh, as we chase, we're being chased.
From the top we go on straight and wild.
We're on our way, I've got to say.
Hey, I want to share your style.
Now here it starts, so don't lose heart.
They're bound to lose to this flavor.
From boot to hood, I feel so good.
I will be free to be, oh yeah.
Share the music, even if I.
Share the one dream, I know where you are.
Share the good times,
share the one world now.
I look up to the stars.
And reach for the sky.
No matter what.
I'll try no matter how high.
So let us go.
Beyond far and wide.
I believe in tomorrow.
If we try.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
I know that you are there.
Just on the other side.
Wait there for me.
Soon it will be you and I.
Then let us go.
Beyond far and wide.
I believe in the one world.
If we try.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Come on, let's go, everybody.
Oh, we share the music.
Come on, let's go, baby, baby.
Oh, we share the one world.
What's the matter?
I heard a loud crash!
Are you okay?
What happened?
Am I seeing things, or is that a man?
What is a man doing on our island?
Shroud yourself from his
leering gaze. Huh? No!
My secret is out.
He saw my back.
Then we mustn't let him
leave the castle alive.
I know it.
What's the big deal?
I just saw her back.
But you know, it's kind of weird.
I could have sworn I've
seen that somewhere before.
What you saw is a secret
we would die to protect.
Or rather, one that we would kill to
protect in this particular instance.
Secret? That thing?
Why is it a secret? Who are you?
Take those questions
to the grave with you.
Love, love, beam.
Hold on, what? What?!
It's a slow, slow beam!
No!
It's making space noise!
Love, love, beam!
Why won't he transform into stone?
Don't tell me he doesn't feel any
excitement after seeing me in the bath.
I am without flaw.
But that's simply beyond
the realm of possibility.
The sublime grandeur of your nude form
can irreparably beguile any creature.
His fear of death must be overwhelming.
The impure urge is within him.
He's a pitiful coward,
but he's a lucky one.
You keep talking about dying, so bye!
I was just looking for
someone important to talk to!
From this high up, he's out of his mind!
I've got him!
Now pistol kick!
What the?
They didn't bounce off me!
What kind of bullets were those?
That man is a dangerous intruder!
Kuja Pirates, go forth and capture him!
Uh, yes, ma 'am.
A man?
How did a man even get here? Who cares?
Let's just go and catch the bastards!
Right.
Get off of me, you stupid snakes!
What kind of snakes are these?
They feel like they're made of iron!
It seems luck is against us.
Let's just hope they skip the
interrogation and kill him right away.
But they'll kill him no
matter what, won't they?
It's with this country.
They were joking when they said
there aren't any men around here.
I'm ready for my explanation
now. Specifically,
I would like to know how you got onto
this island and what you want here.
I don't know.
I'm just as confused as you.
I got sent flying through the sky, and
the next thing I knew, I landed here.
An unlikely story.
Lying to me will only guarantee you
an excruciatingly painful death.
You're here because you want something.
Well, yeah, I could really use a ship.
Actually, it'd be better if you guys
could just give me a lift, though.
Either way, I'm in a pretty big hurry,
and I need to get going right away.
You are the boss around here, right, lady?
So help me out.
Who does this disrespectful
pup think he is?
The snake princess is right.
That story is clearly an
impossible fabrication.
Don't listen to him.
He's plotting something.
You can't deceive us.
We can get back up and keep fighting.
The only way that you will
leave this island is by dying,
and your departure is imminent.
Please, Snake Princess, he's not lying!
I know how this must sound,
but I don't believe this man is the
kind of person who can tell a lie.
What is she doing?
I believe he's telling the truth.
This man is incapable of anything
but a childlike sincerity.
I honestly don't think he would ever
try to inflict any harm upon our land.
Hey, thanks, buddy.
I knew you didn't really want to kill me.
You're one of our warriors, aren't you?
Yes, my name is Margaret.
Given that men are forbidden
here under penalty of death,
he sealed his fate the moment
he arrived in our land.
Why defend him?
Because I share the burden of guilt.
The person who brought him here and
who allowed him into the city...
It was me!
Margaret, no!
You can't!
Snake Princess!
Please, steal your fury!
It was not her fault! It's true!
We found him knocked out and the
floor is totally covered in mushrooms.
We thought he was one of us,
so we brought him back here.
Sweet Pea, Afalandra.
We're just as guilty as Margaret,
but under all those mushrooms,
we just couldn't tell.
It was an honest mistake, Empress.
Stop it, I won't let you do this.
I'm the one who said we should bring
him back to the village, not you.
Does she realize what she's doing?
She's trying to be honest,
but she's just being stupid.
You guys are all right.
You were trying to kill me back there,
but now I see you're actually pretty nice.
I bear the sole responsibility for
bringing the man here, Empress.
Please, Margaret!
It's all right.
Now lift your head,
honest little Margaret.
Love, love, dream!
What the?
Why didn't you keep quiet?
Hold on!
What happened?
What's wrong with you guys?
I turned to stone. Why?
Hey! You!
What the hell did you do?
These three saved my life, you know!
Precisely!
And now they have been justly
punished for their transgression?
Then it's my fault!
Wait!
Turn them back to normal now!
I believe it's time to
release Bekori. Bekori?
The man's already dead and
he doesn't even know it!
I told you to turn them back!
This is the female warrior
nation of Amazon Lily.
Here, strength is regarded as true beauty.
Show us what little
strength you may possess,
and be grateful that I've
given you death in battle.
Behind you stands the
panther known as Bekori.
The beast has served as the official
executioner of Amazon Lily for generations now.
When it's done, there won't be a
single bone left to remember you by.
All I care about is them!
Turn them back now!
Did you hear how that savage was
speaking to the snake princess?
Ceremonic from Lynn Bekori!
Now, Baccarat!
He's strong, he just knocked
Bekori out with a single blow.
And he didn't even use any Haki!
That was just brute strength.
What the hell is wrong with all of you?
That woman up there.
She turned three of your
own people into stone!
How can you just sit up
there and laugh like that?
I never!
That little savage has
the gall to shout at us!
Oh, don't lesser to him!
He's just an animal!
Sure, I feel sorry for those three,
but the Snake Princess had
every right to do what she did!
Of course!
It was justice!
They violated the law of our land!
What you don't understand is that
I'll be forgiven for anything I do.
Absolutely anything.
And the reason why is
because I'm beautiful.
Just look at me.
I'm sure you must agree.
Actually, you make me sick.
Stay strong, sister.
This simply cannot be happening.
There's no man alive that
can resist my allure.
It's just not possible.
So long as that man exists in this
world I shall never know peace again.
How dare you hurt the
snake princess like that!
Make the man suffer for his crimes.
Execute him.
Execute! Execute!
Marigold, Sandersonia, defend
my honor and take his head
Execute! Execute!
You got it We'll get
the job done, big sis.
So these girls have powers, too.
The sisters are about to
start their snake pit dance.
I've never seen Mary Gold's
salamander move before.
I can't wait.
Ooh, don't forget about
Sandersonia's egg-headed serpent!
They look fabulous when they transform!
Of course they do!
It's proof that they've slain the Gorgon!
They've got great looks and
power and must run in the family!
What's a Gorgon?
Is there something I'm missing here?
Just looks like they've
eaten devil fruits to me!
Execution!
Perhaps I'll just swallow him whole.
Or maybe squeeze him to bits.
Grovel all you like, but
we'll still destroy you.
No, it's not like that.
There!
You're not cracked, are you?
Good.
Just wait here, okay?
Real sorry you got turned
into stone because of me.
If Chopper were here, maybe
he could figure something out.
Hopefully you'll go back
to normal again somehow,
like after Aokiji turned
me and Robin into ice.
That's a kind gesture.
But you should be more
concerned about yourself.
Shut up!
I'll do what I want!
Is he trying to?
He's saving Margaret and
the others from harm.
But why he's already been sentenced
to death all done okay which one of
you wants your ass kicked first what
a joke did he just
say what I think
he said if he thinks he can win he's
in for an ugly surprise hilarious
let's find more men to feed to the
gorgon sisters because this is too
Are we still fighting?
I'm ready.
Sure, why not? Love it.
Since you seem intent on winning this
battle, let me give you a little warning.
I wouldn't fall into that pit between
the ring and the seats if I were you.
Well, you could if you wanted to
be impaled on razor-sharp blades.
Don't blink.
This won't take long.
Marigold and Sandersonia,
execute him now for the
crime of sneaking onto
our island and for
personally offending me.
Bestow on him the ultimate punishment.
Will it happen?
Yeah!
Careful now!
He may have some skill after all.
Shoo, Mooseboss!
That's the way, Mara goes!
Crack!
Poison, huh?
That was close.
Powerful poison!
That hurt me, but how?
I'm made of progress.
Told ya, he's all bark and no bite.
But can all men stretch out
and whip around like that?
How fun!
Damn, what's wrong?
Am I not rubber anymore?
No, that's not me.
Then why did it hurt when she hit me?
No fair, man.
You're keeping him all to yourself.
Oh, well.
I've got him now, don't I?
Dammit!
This is hurting, too! Oh, wait a sec.
The same thing happened with that axe guy.
It's exactly like that.
But I don't think he
had Devil Fruit powers.
You have power just like me, huh?
A paramedia type from the look of it.
You can't use Haki then.
Most outsiders never seem to get it.
That's why you're so weak.
That left kick won't work.
Try again.
She knows what I'm about to do.
Snake?
Oh, yes! Crush him!
That didn't hurt a bit. Nice.
I'm back to normal.
Gum-Gum, step away!
Dance.
She's so fast.
And with her Haki, she can see every
attack as soon as that loud thing set up.
You're really simple-minded.
I can read you like a book.
How is she doing that?
I can't get a punch in on her.
Seems you're forgetting about someone.
Snake stick!
Dammit!
You better be careful.
You might fall off the edge.
He's falling into the pit!
Okay, okay, okay.
That was almost bad.
The snake princess just pushed
her hair back behind her ear.
Her beauty knows no bounds.
She's just perfect.
He's the very definition
of all bark and no bite.
He is funny, though.
Hey, lady! You suck!
Oh! Oh!
How rude!
The audacity!
Teach him a lesson! Come on!
Steward the beast!
No mercy!
Sonia! Marigold!
Kill him!
I can't tolerate him a moment longer!
We must ensure once and for all
that his filthy outbursts are silenced.
Well, you heard our big sister.
It's a pity we can't prolong your pain.
Indeed, sister, but at the very least,
we'll show him a taste of despair.
Whoa!
What the hell are you doing?
You leave her alone!
Hey! Stop!
You're gonna end up breaking her!
Good idea.
She saved your life you
said then she deserves
it there you have it sis we found a new
way to Make him suffer
before he dies don't
be stupid this is a duel
between you two and me
I'm afraid you're the only
one who thought this was
a duel this is clearly a
public execution Compared
to the trauma you caused
our poor sister this is
the least we can do to
you In this proud nation,
all of the women look up
to the Snake Princess.
Her beauty is unparalleled.
She's strong and noble.
She's called the Pirate
Empress, Boa Hancock.
You know how she felt?
She loves this country, and
this is how you treat her?
Our Empress is popular.
Your friend would agree
with her punishment.
Like hell she would!
What are you?
Some kind of idiot? How rude.
Such language.
It will turn these
self-sacrificing friends
of hers into pretty
little piles of rubble.
Three... No! Don't do it!
Two...
Careful.
One.
No! Margaret!
I said stop! That's enough!
Ah!
The warriors are fainting!
Absurd.
It can't be.
What a relief.
She's not cracked or broken or anything.
Alright, guess you're not so bad, huh?
Ha ha ha ha ha!
Unreal!
That was the Conqueror's spirit!
You're kidding!
Only one out of a million people
can someone for that Haki!
Let alone control it!
I've never seen anyone besides our
big sister do something like that!
This boy has the qualities of a Conqueror!
The ability to stand above all others!
The same as me.
There's no doubt about it.
He wields such power.
But who the hell is this boy?
Is he toying with us?
Am I dreaming?
That didn't really just happen, did it?
What the heck's everyone babbling about?
What's the big deal?
Did I miss something?
I don't think he realizes
he who's talking.
I guess he doesn't know
how to control it, then.
All right.
I get it now.
You two girls are really strong.
Back to the duel.
Round two.